# RANDY PANOPIO

randypanopio.github.io randypanopio@gmail.com 778 - 926 - 8693 Vancouver, B.C

Design oriented developer with a focus on building usable and maintainable tools. With a diverse background of user experience and web development, to cinematography and physical art. I try to bridge ideas and build sustainable products in all of the projects that I partake in.

## **Work Experience**

# Electronic Arts Associate Technical Artist

Burnaby, British Columbia Sept 2021 - Feb 2023

Worked on pipeline tool development and management to deliver art assets from content creation to in game render. Supported multiple FIFA/FC titles including titles from 22, 23, the FC rebrand, FIFA Online, FIFA Mobile, and unreleased incubation football titles.

- Subject matter expert on content management, and worked on designing and replacing the delivery pipeline, tripling the previous workflow's throughput and reducing process runtime from a 10 minute run down to 1 minute, while introducing previously unsupported content into this automated framework. Supporting over a hundred thousand unique files and assets per year.
- Collaborated and supported cross domain teams and multiple international teams to organize, process, and deliver content into the game while maintaining production timelines.
- Enhanced DCC (Digital Content Creation) tools, modernized legacy pipelines through code updates and moving towards automations, including migrations to new in-house technologies. Developed new tools to streamline and automate repetitive tasks for artists and management. Provided training and support on production workflows and tools.

# Under the GUI Academy Inc. **Programming Instructor**

Vancouver, British Columbia
Dec 2020 - June 2021

Taught children ages 7 - 16 concepts of programming through hands on Unity and website projects during weekly online class sessions.

- Introduced concepts regarding programming foundations, web development, and game design to children with various skill levels.
- Volunteered creating personalized coding projects and challenges for advanced students who showed interest in expanding their programming repertoire.

# Safe Software Inc. Front-End Web Developer - Co-op

Surrey, British Columbia May 2018 - Dec 2018

Acted as a front-end developer and the primary interface designer, integrating myself within an agile workflow, maintaining and building web interfaces for a suite of enterprise GIS management tools.

- Collaborated with a team of developers, product managers, and stakeholders working on a new core feature, on an enterprise web application used by over 10,000 organizations worldwide.
- Implemented three new UI for new features built upon existing management tools with over 100 individual UI elements within 3 design iterations, and completed within a rigorous 4 month testing phase.
- Worked in an agile and test-driven development environment, building upon a hybrid web framework application while authoring and maintained unit tests during production.

## **Projects**

## Freelance Developer On-Call

**2020 - Ongoing** 

Semi-active developer in the indie industry, and in the open source environment as a whole.

- Developed and contributed to open-source projects, including companion web applications leveraging game data, as well as native plugins and applications for streaming activities. Published and available on my personal GitHub portfolio.
- Contributed to projects and released some of my own. Developing in-house content management systems, importers, and various in-game systems. Working on procedural level editors, dialogue/interaction systems, internal design tools, character Al, and various gameplay systems.

## Education

## **Skills**

#### **Simon Fraser University**

Interactive Arts and Technology (SIAT), Bachelor of Science -Concentration of Interactive Systems 2015 - 2020

#### Development

Languages: C#, Python, Java, PS Web: FE stack, PHP, JS Libraries Version: Git, Perforce, GitHub API Development & Integrations

#### **Content Creation**

Texturing & Processing (PS) 3D Modeling (Maya, Blender) Character Rigging FK/IK Animations

#### **Toolkit**

Maya Scripting (MayaPy, PyMEL) Jira, Shotgrid (Integrations) UI: Web, PySide, Qt Shaders (Shader Graphs)